<resources>
    <string name="player_error">Error initializing YouTube player: %s</string>
    <string name="seek_to">Jump To</string>
    <string name="seek_to_hint">Seconds</string>
    <string name="app_name">SounD CHK</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_camera">QR Code Reader</string>
    <string name="menu_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="menu_favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="text_read_QR">Reading QR Code...</string>
    <string name="title_activity_story_page">StoryPageActivity</string>

    <string name="read_more">"Tap to Unlock with QR Code to READ MORE"</string>

    <string name="griffs_short_text">
        "THE DOC WILL SEE YOU NOW\n"

        "Dr. Griffs\n\n"

        "Written by Ruairi Conway\n\n"

        "Aleem Griffiths is taking on life with a PhD in Partyology. This self-taught disc jockey"
        "is on a mission to make your day, and with a grin like his how can he fail? Dubbed Dr. Griffs"
        "a.k.a. The Doctor a.k.a. Mr. Caribash a.k.a. Mr. DecipherThisYouMay, his character and charisma"
        "go from strength to strength. But he is more than music. That’s just the tip of his entrepreneurial"
        "iceberg. You’ll find his name across a range of merchandise, a platform on YouTube, and photography"
        "has found a home in his heart too.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="griffs_long_text">
        "As the youngest of five siblings living in the South Bronx, he grew up in a family of chess"
        "players. Chess played a big roll in Griffith’s early life, it kept him amongst the right people"
        "and he and his brothers shared a passion for it.\n\n"

        "“I didn’t have a problem with playing chess but I always knew there was more to life than"
        "following directly in their footsteps."\n\n"

        "Not sure of his own footsteps just yet, his sisters convinced him to join a program called"
        "BuildOn. During his sophomore and junior years of high school, Griffiths traveled to"
        "impoverished areas of Mali and Nicaragua and helped with the construction of amenities"
        "such as schools. It left a mark on Griffiths and opened his eyes to what good he could give"
        "back to this floating green and blue rock of ours.\n\n"

        "This perspective focused Griffiths on an immensely ambitious life goal;“Millionaire by 27, billionaire by 35”."

        "How does one go about reaching these goals? You grind. Aleem found his way to the University"
        "of Rochester and has squeezed every ounce of opportunity from this city. Holding onto his"
        "billionaire mindset he knew a conventional job would not help him reach his goal. That’s when"
        "fate gave him a wink and a nudge. During his freshman year, a graduating senior that Griffiths"
        "had befriended asked him to take his spot as one of the regular Djs on campus.\n\n"

        "“I jumped on the idea. DJing wasn’t something I had ever done before. In fact, at that point"
        "in my life I had only been to like 4 or 5 parties. I lived in the hood and my mother sheltered"
        "me from that.”\n\n"

        "It took a little time for Griffiths to find his feet on a side of the musical world that"
        "he was unaccustomed to. Griffiths was starting from the ground up.\n\n"

        "“Because of this, when I would go to parties, I would document a party from start to finish."
        "I would try to understand exactly what was being played and how they were playing it”.\n\n"

        "Pouring over lists of parties past, he recorded the DJs every move. He documented each track"
        "played and would rate every transition. While everyone partied and danced the night away,"
        "Dr. Griffiths was looking for enlightenment.\n\n"

        "“I would do this pretty religiously for every party I went to especially if it’s a DJ"
        "I haven’t heard before. I wouldn’t copy their playlist but if I was stuck during a party"
        "that I was DJing, looking through my notes could help me get out of a tight spot”.\n\n"

        "We all know that every good DJ needs a good name so why Dr. Griffs? Well during senior year"
        "everyone was putting names on their class hoodies. Excited about the prospect Griffiths"
        "debated having “Da Griffs” in homage to “Da Bronx”, but he had a change of heart."\n\n"

        "“I’m going to college, I’m going to be professional, so I should put doctor. College = PhD = Doctor,"
        "know what I’m saying?”\n\n"

        "And so Dr. Griffs was born.\n\n"

        "“My dad was from Jamaica (He passed away when Griffiths was 10), and my mom is from St. Thomas."
        "Because of this reggae has always been a big part of my life. [We] lived above a bodega so"
        "there was always Latin based music being blasted below me and the cars driving by my block"
        "would always play the latest rap and hip hop songs.”\n\n"

        "Even his siblings are responsible for guiding Griffiths taste in some way. Theme songs from"
        "anime shows and the teenage angst of fallout boy played a big part and I’m sure we can all"
        "relate to that sentiment.\n\n"

        "“My block was filled with people from the Caribbean, Mexico, Africa everything really except"
        "people from Europe. There was no white people on my block which is probably why I’m not an EDM DJ."
        "So I guess all of that combined kinda help craft my style”\n\n"

        "DJing quickly became Dr. Griffs passion and now that he had a name, some basics, and a style,"
        "the only thing left to do was dive head first into it.\n\n"

        "“I tried, tried, and kept trying and while I was DJing I picked up confidence in myself”.\n\n"

        "As that confidence has continued to grow, so has his following. He’s now a regular on the local"
        "circuit appearing at venues such as Bar 145 and there’s nothing but good vibes resonating from"
        "anyone who’s danced to the Doctors beats.\n\n"

        "Working under Bdubd Enterprise, a local promotional group, has given Griffiths a huge lift.\n\n"

        "“Thanks to Bdubd I almost always had a platform to DJ every week. As I got better, opportunities"
        "on campus became better for me through different organizations like the BSU (Black Students Union),"
        "SALSA (A Latin dance/music club), and the DLH (Douglas Leadership House) started reaching out to me.”\n\n"

        "Griffiths is a thoroughly active member of the universities life. He himself is a member of"
        "the Douglas Leadership House. He first encountered them back in 2013 during his freshman year.\n\n"

        "Following racially charged incidents on campus, he followed a demonstration organized by the DLH"
        "and BSU. He was in awe of the power and integrity they displayed. After joining their ranks he"
        "became the DLH historian. This is where photography found its way into his mix.\n\n"

        "“DJing inspired me to take photography seriously, my beat making seriously and now my merch.”\n\n"

        "The list doesn’t end there, Griffiths has also begun voicing his thoughts and opinions on YouTube.\n\n"

        "Right now Dr. Griffs is riding a wave of popularity. The merchandise he speaks off is popping"
        "up all over the local communities social media. It’s simple but if you give people a clever"
        "t-shirt design with some bold colors, the orders come flooding in, and voila, you have walking"
        "billboards with your name on them. It’s been a huge success for Griffiths.\n\n"

        "Looking to the future, looking to Rochester and looking to graduation, Griffiths is excited"
        "to give back to the communities that he’s enjoyed and learned from. “My favorite venue to DJ"
        "at is Water Street Music Hall. Every time I’ve DJed there it was for a huge party Bdubd’s"
        "Halloween party. Rochester being a city of a lot of jazz Giants and Eastman there’s a lot of musical potential.”\n\n"

        "What’s next for Dr. Griffs? Well on top of studying for finals there’s DJing, photography,"
        "producing his own original beats, creating YouTube videos and leading the DLH, it looks like"
        "he’s got his hands full. But he’s taking it in his stride. The only way is up and you can"
        "guarantee he’ll find his sweet spot.\n\n"

        "As Dr. Griffs would say #DecipherThisAsYouMay\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="little_short_text">
        "THE LITTLE BOX\n\n"

        "Written by Nina Listro\n\n"

        "Our crew walked into The Little Box around 7:30pm on the evening of one of their shows. The"
        "main entrance, a sliding glass door, opened immediately to the kitchen where the producers"
        "were cooking up enchiladas. Without hesitation, we were offered beers and a seat on their couch.\n\n"

        "As you may have guessed, the place is anything but you’re conventional music venue. It’s a house"
        "- a typical college rental just across the river from the University of Rochester. Four university"
        "seniors live, eat and sleep there, occasionally hosting gigs in their basement.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="little_long_text">
        "Bob is one of the four students that live in the house. Upon our arrival, he was in the basement"
        "taking the time to jam out on his own before the bands showed up. The night’s line up would"
        "consist of four Rochester-based acts: Apollo 11, Sabrina Nichols of Slumbers, Rash and Lung Cycles.\n\n"

        "Although some of Bob’s responsibilities have been diffused he still serves as the poster child"
        "for the venue. Bob MCs every show, is in charge of all things audio, and can be seen wandering"
        "the house, making sure everyone is happy and having a good time.\n\n"

        "Apollo 11, scheduled as the first act of the night, arrived shortly after us. Bob helped"
        "them get settled in the basement and then joined us in the living room. The room itself"
        "writes a narrative about the gang’s musical devotion. Album covers plaster the walls; there’s"
        "Tame Impala’s Currents, Is This It by The Strokes, 6 Feet Beneath The Moon by King Krule,"
        "Flying Lotus’ You’re Dead - the list goes on. Someone turned on an ambient track I’m unfamiliar"
        "with and everyone seems at ease; it was a chill Friday night.\n\n"

        "Bob thanked us for coming. Although he was excited that we wanted to highlight The Little Box,"
        "he asked us to change his name and to keep out any photos that could give away the gig’s location.\n\n"

        "Apparently his landlord would not be too impressed if he found out that the gang was putting"
        "on shows in the basement. We assured him we’d follow those rules and, instantly relaxing"
        "back into himself, we began chatting about how The Little Box came to be.\n\n"

        "When Bob and his friends were looking for a house at the beginning of their junior year,"
        "they already had it in mind that they were going to host shows. Inspiration for The Little"
        "Box came about because the off-campus music scene seemed to have petered out over the years."
        "Bob and Co. wanted to revitalize it.\n\n"

        "“I think I went to every single show they had,” said Bob. “I immediately fell in love with it all.”\n\n"

        "When he was a freshman, Bob remembers going to Laundromat 19, another 19th ward college residency"
        "that hosted basement shows on the regular.\n\n"

        "After the students who ran Laundromat 19 graduated, there was the Radio House on Genesee Street"
        "that held similar things, but there was still a void that Bob wanted to refill. It didn’t take"
        "too long for the boys to set up their first show after they moved into the house that then"
        "became The Little Box. In October of 2015, Bob and Co. held their first show over Meliora Weekend,"
        "where the groups Ligaments/Vinton Surf, Lung Cycles and mankind performed. Overall, however,"
        "the venued didn’t have much momentum in the beginning, months passing by between shows.\n\n"

        "“It was pretty hard to make room for [the music] with school and stuff,” said Bob. Makes sense,"
        "too. Junior year is sometimes the most critical for undergraduate students, especially those"
        "who are looking to apply to graduate school.\n\n"

        "This past summer, however, things began to pick up - five shows have already happened so far"
        "since the start of 2017 - and Bob and Co. rarely find themselves having to reach out to bands."
        "Instead, the bands either contact The Little Box themselves or they’re directed over by Tim"
        "Avery of The Bug Jar if he can’t place them there. Just saying the name “Tim Avery” makes Bob"
        "starstruck; his eyes, his smile both grew wide as he spoke about him.\n\n"

        "“Having Tim do this is just… it’s just, it’s just so incredible,” he stammered. “It makes"
        "it feel like we’re a legit music venue.”\n\n"

        "With that, as if right on queue, we heard music starting from down below in the basement."
        "During our conversation, guests had flooded the house and it began to get almost too busy"
        "and loud to continue the discussion.\n\n"

        "“Well, I guess it’s time to listen to some music,” said Bob and we all began the descent downstairs."
        "It was packed with college-aged attendees head bobbing away to the folk fusion that Apollo"
        "11 has to offer. We tried to squeeze by, shimmying through the crowd in search of the perfect"
        "spot to set up the cameras. The only empty(ish) corner was the dedicated laundry area. We fiddled"
        "around with the tripod, trying to dodge drying racks and swaying bodies.\n\n"

        "It was quite dark down there in the basement, the only source of light being a makeshift"
        "stringlight chandelier, which made it hard to snag any super clear shots. But, looking back"
        "at it, it was probably a good thing. First of all, it made Bob less nervous that his landlord"
        "would be able to pinpoint from the blurry photos and secondly, I’m not sure a completely"
        "comprehensible photo would do the gig any justice.\n\n"

        "There’s something more here than just good music; the atmosphere is wholesome and intimate."
        "Even when the set finishes and the crowd heads up stairs while the next act sets up, the cohesive,"
        "friendly environment remains. There are friends sharing laughs with friends, strangers striking"
        "up conversation and band members hanging out, drinking some beers; the whole vibe really quite special.\n\n"

        "Bob told me he and some of his other housemates are planning to stay in Rochester after"
        "graduation and intend to keep The Little Box going. The only thing he said might change is the crowd.\n\n"

        "“Right now we have mostly U of R students coming to the shows,” he says, “but we’ll be entering"
        "the workforce soon and those communities will most likely be incorporated.”\n\n"

        "All in all, however, the venue will most likely stay the same in terms of operation and character."
        "It’s more than just a house party, it’s about experiencing music in a novel way.\n\n"

        "“I think The Little Box opens people’s eyes,” says Bob. “They seem to have this distinction"
        "between normal people and what they think a musician is. At The Little Box, they realize"
        "that there are people out there who aren’t famous at all but still make incredible art.”\n\n"
    </string>


    <string name="juicy_short_text">
        "JUICE FUNK\n\n"

        "Juicy Connotation\n\n"

        "Interview by Christian Cieri"

        "How did you guys meet and what brought you together?\n\n"

        "Thomas:\nTell them the story about how you met Ryan.\n\n"

        "Chris:\nI don’t know dude this could come back to haunt me\n\n"

        "Thomas:\n
        Alright, so he met Ryan in an elevator and they were like YO we should jam sometime\n\n"

        "Chris:\n
        That was a good summary\n\n"

        "Thomas:\n
        So Ryan was all sketched out\n\n"

        "Ryan:\n
        I wasn’t sketched out?\n\n"

        "Everyone starts telling their version of the story\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="juicy_long_text">
        "Chris:\nAlright this needs to be corrected.\n"
        "So I’m playing in a folk band with Thomas and Jordan; Thomas was playing guitar and Jordan was"
        "playing upright bass, I was playing the Djembe. We were looking for a band name and we’re"
        "sold on Juicy Connotation, I was obsessed with it. But Tom was saying “we’re not Juicy"
        "Connotation, the name is sick but this is not Juicy Connotation. Trust me dude, we’ll make"
        "a funk band and it’ll be Juicy Connotation. I was like “sure man” like I never expected this"
        "to happen, but what do you know? So the name preceded the band.\n"

        "Then one day I’m randomly in an elevator and I see this dude Ryan and I was acting wild,"
        "you know what I mean? I had seen him around and walked by his room before as he’s playing"
        "the guitar so I’m like “Yo dude I fuck with your guitar playing” that was the extent of"
        "how I knew him. So I keep shouting “Yo dude we should jam sometime man, it’s good to see"
        "you again,” and he says “Yup we should man”. and I said “How about tomorrow?”\n"

        "So last second we hustle a bunch of people together, with Ryan, I hit up Jordan, Thomas"
        "brings his Saxophone and Juicy Connotation was in its formative moments.\n\n"

        "Thomas:\n
        We only jammed once before Alex came along. We met Alex randomly. I sat down with him one day"
        "because I had seen him around the place and he said, “Music is the one thing, the only thing"
        "that seems to matter” and I was like “Man you just said the magic words, come jam with us”."
        "So we got together, Me, Ryan, Chris, Jordan and now Alex, and it just clicked perfectly.\n\n"

        "How did you guys come up with the name in the first place?\n\n"

        "Chris:\n
        We were in Gilbert 3 Lounge [University of Rochester]\n\n"

        "Thomas:\n
        We were just writing a bunch of names on whiteboard thinking, “What the fuck do we call ourselves?”"
        "We had “Taj Mahal” up there, we had “Silver Lining”, but the word “Connotation” stuck out.\n\n"

        "Chris:\n
        So then my buddy Big Sam walks in “YO SAM WHAT’S YOUR FAVORITE ADJECTIVE?” He just says “Juicy” and walks away.\n\n"

        "Chris:\n
        As soon as he said it I was like “OH MY GOD juicy connotation, fucking Juicy Connotation”."
        "And there you have it… “Juicy Connotation” was born.\n\n"

        "Not many people can pin down what your style is, how would you describe it?\n\n"

        "Everyone in unison “Juice Funk”\n\n"

        "Ryan:\n
        We self labeled it “Juice Funk”, which is not a real Genre but we call it a blend of Jazz and funk.\n\n"

        "Argument about how it’s not a blend of Jazz and Funk ensues.\n
        Points are made about diminished chords as a qualifier.\n
        The word Fusion is thrown around.\n\n"

        "Jordan: There you go, I’d call it fusion. What we do agree on is the “Juice Funk” part.\n\n"

        "What or who influenced the style? What bands have influenced you? What brought you to Juice Funk?\n\n"

        "Alex:\n
        Well Jamiroquai’s Bassist was the reason that Jordan started playing electric, we recently"
        "stumbled across moonchild which is really good, Vulfpeck is super funky, Snarky Puppy is"
        "one of my biggest influences, Tauk is a smaller four piece instrumental group.\n\n"

        "Thomas:\n
        John Mayer\n
        John Schofield\n
        John Coltrane\n\n"

        "A lot of Johns\n\n"

        "Alex:\n
        But as far as the Fusion goes lately there’s been a lot of 80s influence\n\n"

        "Chris:\n
        I think lately there’s been a lot of The Dip as well.\n\n"

        "Have you guys been busy since the release of your album “Freshly Squeezed”?\n\n"

        "Thomas:\n
        Oh we’ve been busy. Since the release in February last year we wrote four new songs by the end of that"
        "year and continued to write. We took a break for that semester because people studied abroad"
        "and since we’ve been back this semester we’ve done a lot of writing and a lot of jamming"
        "and solidifying our sound.\n\n"

        "Alex:
        We had almost an EPs worth of music, new music, ready to go before Freshly squeezed was even released."
        "We recorded what was going to be an EP but then that never happened. Basically we had more"
        "ready to go immediately after the album came out.\n\n"

        "Thomas:
        The next thing is the self-titled album we want to have out by the end of next year. The primary"
        "goal is definitely to start recording that.\n\n"

        "Chris:
        We’ve also been gigging quite a bit this past semester at a few cool places like the Temple"
        "bar and Grill and The Bug Jar. We have one coming up at the ButaPub too.\n\n"

        "What has been your favorite performance so far?\n\n"

        "Chris:
        We had a four-hour slot at Temple, which was huge. We got to improvise for so long, the sheer duration was amazing.\n\n"

        "Alex:
        We had to play everything we had AND Jam for a straight hour or more. Plus my folks came out"
        "from Massachusetts and the guy who engineered our first show came out too so that was nice.\n\n"

        "Chris:
        Dude, he’s at all our shows.\n\n"

        "Ryan:
        This drunken girl came up to us afterwards and handed us a wad of cash. She bought everyone"
        drinks which was pretty cool too.\n\n"

        "So on the other end of the spectrum, what has been the worst performance?\n\n"

        "Hollers of anguish erupt shouting “D-Day” (Dandelion day).\n\n"

        "Thomas:
        This was our fourth or fifth show and it was cold as fuck. I had rolled out of bed to go to"
        "this show with the flu and my fingers couldn’t move because it was so fucking cold. I was"
        "playing the same fucking scale in every song just up and down.\n\n"

        "Jordan:
        I used a kitchen knife to cut off the fingers of my gloves. We had heat cannons pointed at"
        "the stage and they were doing nothing. This Kid had Reynaud’s Syndrome."

        "Ryan:
        Yeah, I have poor circulation in my hands and feet so I was just dead on the stage. We slowed"
        "all of our songs down by like 100 bpm. It was impossible. It sucked.\n\n"

        "What do you think about the music scene in Rochester? And will it always be Juicy Connotations home?\n\n"

        "Alex:
        My interpretation of the music scene in Rochester is a really cool one. Everyone kind of"
        "knows everyone. It’s small enough that you can get your foot in the door and be playing places"
        "quickly, it’s not like you need a label behind you. You can get into smaller venues and you"
        "can get into the scene quickly. You even have Eastman, which is a hub for a lot of the"
        "conservatory style music.\n\n"

        "Jordan:
        I feel like there’s such a difference between the university scene and the Rochester music scene."
        "They’re like completely different things. So the University is kind of all over the place,"
        "you have a few bands around the river campus and a few up at Eastman but then there are the"
        "actual city Bands that we never actually hear of.\n\n"

        "Alex:
        True, there is this huge underground, not even underground, hip hop scene too. We have played"
        "for an artist named Tru Starr. He’s based out of Rochester, so that’s hip hop, soul hop type"
        "of stuff. There’s a good mix of cultures and it’s small enough that you can play around and"
        "everyone is welcome. I don’t think you can talk about the music scene without talking about"
        "Arjun Baxter. He’s the guy that everyone knows but he just moved to Philly. I played with him"
        "with I.Am.Tru.Starr and he was involved with several other bands.\n\n"

        "He’s a character. He had a farewell show and four of his bands played but he only joined"
        "two of them. But everyone loved him and he shows that it’s small enough to make it but you"
        "can still be paid well. But everyone loved him and he shows that it’s small enough to make"
        "it but you can still be paid well.\n\n"

        "Thomas:
        Is it home? For the band? Yeah I guess we all met here and at the end of next year [graduation],"
        "unless something crazy happens, odds are that’s it, right? Saying this is Juicy’s home is"
        "probably an appropriate statement.\n\n"

        "So what is your creative process? How do you get to a finished song?\n\n"

        "Thomas:
        I promise you this is how every song comes about. One person has some melodic idea, and then"
        "they’ll start playing it, then somebody else will join in, and somebody else will join in"
        "and we’ll improvise on it. We’ll jam and jam and jam until one melody stands out and we’re"
        "all vibing on this one melody. We get one or two sections together and then we piece together"
        "the inbetweens, the intro / outro etc.\n\n"

        "Jordan:
        I mean these jam sessions are hours long, we take them so far, we take them into space, take"
        "the song into places where it breaks down and no one can even continue playing their instrument"
        "anymore and then we’re like “At least there was good shit in there.”\n\n"

        "Chris:
        Every time we play, we record it. That’s how most of them are birthed. We listen back to it"
        "and we’re looking for the best spots and try to replicate those moments in our next session.\n\n"

        "Do you have any pre-performance rituals?\n\n"

        "Ryan:
        I can’t be standing next to a white column within an hour of the show.\n\n"

        "Chris:
        That’s true\n\n"

        "Jordan:
        Yeah, yeah, yeah, I always change my socks. I flip the left sock to the right foot and my right sock to my left foot.\n\n"

        "Ryan:
        I try and put my right shoe next to my bed…\n\n"

        "Alex:
        You guys are so convincing that they actually think you’re crazy.\n"

        "In fairness, they did have our team bamboozled\n\n"

        "Thomas:
        We don’t have any rituals but we try to jam to get in the same mind frame.\n\n"

        "Alex:
        If we’re playing on a list with a few bands we’ll usually get together before we go on and"
        "hang for while. Just chill together in the green room or something.\n\n"

        "Jordan:
        You make it sound like we play some mad legit gigs, a green room?\n\n

        "As long as it doesn’t have any white poles and has a spot to swap socks\n\n"

        "What are the big plans for the future?\n\n"

        "Chris:
        The thing is we all have extremely different aspirations for what we want.\n\n"

        "Thomas:
        Alright, if I had to put money on it, I would say that Ryan and Jordan are going to get jobs"
        "immediately after college, Chris is probably going to figure out some place where music is"
        "really good and to continue with whatever music he can. And then Alex is probably going to"
        "go work on a farm.\n\n"

        "Alex scoffs at the thought\n\n"

        "Chris:
        Basically the three of us are trying to make it big [Thomas, Alex and Chris] in the music industry. That’s our main aspiration.\n\n"

        "Thomas:
        I don’t think I’ve even asked you two [Ryan and Jordan] yet what you want but with that being"
        "said I think there’s a lot of potential. When we played at Temple, that drunken girl that came"
        "up to us, she said we were way to good to be playing in bars and I think she’s right. We have"
        "this crazy tight chemistry and this formality to our sound that could get us into well paying gigs."
        "If we throw some spice in there, some crazy shit…\n\n"

        "Ryan:
        Oregano\n\n"

        "Thomas:
        Yeah with some oregano, we could make some waves\n\n"

        "Alex:
        I just thought she was drunk\n\n"

        "Thomas:
        If we put our heads together I think we could make a huge splash.\n\n"
    </string>



    <string name="paxton_short_text">
        "Del Paxton - “All Day, Every Day, All Night”\n\n"

        "By Nathan Raymond\n\n"

	    "Del Paxton is a three-piece rock group from Buffalo, New York which formed in 2013. With"
        "the help of Topshelf Records, the band released their debut full-length ‘All Day, Every Day"
        ", All Night’ on March 3rd, 2017. The release offers 11 songs, each infectiously catchy punk"
        "and pop-rock tunes with technical, math-rock undertones.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="paxton_long_text">
        "While Del Paxton’s music is often energetic, loud, and crunchy, there are plenty of"
        "atmospheric guitar riffs and vocal harmonies to compliment this, resulting in an album that"
        "is both sonically and emotionally dynamic. Tracks such as ‘Loose Leaf’ and ‘Wrong Distance’"
        "affirm the band’s driving punk and emo influences, while ‘Koolwink’ and ‘Thermos’ channel"
        "more of a pop-rock delivery.\n\n"

        "Guitarist and vocalist, Dylan England, writes lyrics that are both memorable and highly"
        "relatable, often regarding day-to-day activities such as taking long drives or embarking"
        "on introspective walks home. Bassist, Zack Schoedel, offers harmonies to add depth to"
        "Dylan’s catchy vocal melodies, and he even takes the lead with his own smart, personal"
        "lyrics on tracks such as ‘Take It To The Limit’ and ‘Primetime’. While Dylan executes"
        "well-crafted leads, and Zack rips technically-configured melodies, all of this is held"
        "together by Greg McClure’s tasteful drumming. Greg cleverly incorporates jerky shifts in"
        "rhythm and spastic fills to guide Dylan and Zack towards unexpected changes in tempo."
        "This makes listening to Del Paxton a highly interesting and involved experience. Whether"
        "you’re a fan of angsty emo-revival bands such as Snowing, or if you have a soft spot for"
        "90’s pop-rock groups like Third Eye Blind, there is no shortage of beautifully-constructed,"
        "heartfelt tracks for you to enjoy.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="rosehip_short_text">
        "Rosehip - “Sore”\n\n"

        "By Nick Raymond\n\n"

        "If you’re looking for an atmospheric, acoustic singer-songwriter record that’s extremely relaxing but equally emotional, then look no further than"
        "Rosehip’s new EP titled Sore. These five tracks consist of lush acoustic guitars which perfectly complement the gentle voice of Mackenzie Harris.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="rosehip_long_text">
        "While Sore is a sonically pleasant listen, Rosehip’s melancholy, detailed lyrics are what"
        "give these tracks depth. Whether she is contemplating her relationship with her parents,"
        "such as in the opening track, “6:28 AM”, or ruminating on a lost love on “Unruly Lover”,"
        "Rosehip has the power to transport the listener into her emotional state by using only a"
        "few words.\n\n"

        "While the bulk of this EP is filled with angst and sadness, there are some playful and"
        "humorous lyrics on the standout track “14th Colony”. As the record’s sole upbeat tune,"
        "this pop-influenced track provides a refreshing change of pace by showcasing charisma and"
        "personality. The second verse is particularly care-free, as Rosehip sings  “Let's get"
        "married today / Blind eye to what is happening / Even if we're not in love, / The tax"
        "breaks cut it I'm sure” over a staccatoed acoustic rhythm. But before it ends, Rosehip"
        "flips the song on it’s head by giving a gloomier depiction of not being in love"
        "(“But it's true, what they say We're not in love, none to blame 'Cause I'm inclined to"
        "stop short from the start). This clever trick allows “14th Colony” to flow seamlessly"
        "into the rest of the otherwise downcast EP. All in all, this record is the perfect"
        "soundtrack to a grey-skied, rainy afternoon. If a full length record from Rosehip is in"
        "the cards, it will undoubtedly be worth a listen.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="wagoneer_short_text">
        "Grand Wagoneer - “Reservoir”\n\n"

        "By Nick Raymond\n\n"

        "“I\'d self describe as a non-believing acolyte\nhalf-heartedly agreeing to everything to avoid a fight“"

        "\n\nThese are the first words sung on Grand Wagoneer\’s debut record titled Reservoir. The"
        "confessional and intimate lyrics here are a good indication of the story that will be told"
        "throughout the album. Nostalgia for love lost, self-deprecation, and religion are some of"
        "the recurring themes that Grand Wagoneer - aka Ben Schmitz - analyzes with sharp detail"
        "and stunning imagery on many of the tracks. Lyrically, this album fits snuggly into the "
        "recent wave of sadcore/emo music that has been sweeping the underground as of late.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="wagoneer_long_text">
        "But while the direct, emotional lyrics are the core of the record, it is the varied instrumentation that makes this body"
        "of work stand out from the rest. The opening track, “Diplomat”, takes the form of a mellow singer/songwriter tune with shimmering,"
        "layered acoustic guitars, tinged by plucking banjos and a mesmerizing keyboard riff that drives the song. What makes Reservoir so"
        "special is its authentic blend of many different genres, all of which Schmitz pulls off earnestly and effortlessly.\n\n"

        "The album’s third track is the true gem of the album. “Charlotte” is a piano-driven, Ben Folds-esque tune accompanied by"
        "epic baroque style horns. The narrative is a sad tale about a first love forbidden by his parents due to their religious beliefs."
        "But the grand instrumentation emphasizes the joy of the relationship, rather than ruminating on its abrupt demise.\n\n"

        "Many of the following songs make use of the electric guitar - particularly on the brooding track appropriately titled"
        "“Thumping and Thrashing”, and the energetic interlude “The Year in Review”, which sounds inspired by 90s indie bands"
        "such as Built to Spill.\n\n"

        "For an album of 11 songs, this record covers a lot of musical ground. Alternating between soft acoustic music such as"
        "on the minimalistic ballad “Say Goodbye”, guitar-driven indie rock on “Empire State”, and electronic loops on the"
        "reflective title track, is not an easy task. But Schmitz doesn’t just makes it work - he makes it work incredibly well."
        "As a result, Reservoir is a musically unpredictable, lyrically relatable, and wholly impressive record that is an extremely"
        "satisfying listening experience.\n\n"
    </string>


    <string name="artawake_short_text">
        "ArtAwake 2017!\n\n"

        "By Nathan Raymond\n\n"

        "Each year, students at the University of Rochester who are determined to promote the"
        "presence of art and music in our community join forces to host ArtAwake – an all-day art"
        "and music festival featuring a beautiful variety of art installations and music performances"
        "by local artists. On April 8th, the event was held at Rettner Hall on the University of"
        "Rochester campus. I managed to catch a few of the musical acts, and I was wildly impressed with what I heard.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="artawake_long_text">
        "Performing right outside of Rettner hall in the calm Spring air, I caught ‘Simba Marimba’,"
        "an African music group from the Eastman School of Music. The ensemble consists of only"
        "percussive instruments, all various types of marimbas aside from the drum set. The marimbas"
        "dramatically range in size, where the smaller high-pitched instruments hold the melody,"
        "and the larger lower-pitched marimbas are used for rhythm and bass. The tunes that the"
        "ensemble played were all joyful, enthusiastic, and incredibly technical. Playing these advanced"
        "marimba parts must have demanded some serious hand-eye coordination skills. However, what"
        "was even more impressive was the degree to which the Simba Marimba ensemble’s music radiated"
        "love and happiness in their art. This was clearly evident by a quick survey of the audience,"
        "as we all watched with wonder and smiles upon our faces.\n\n"

        "Another highlight of the evening was catching Tart Vandelay perform on the third floor of"
        "Rettner Hall. While the full-band typically contains four members, Katie Halligan"
        "(Vocals/Synth/Ukelele) and Martin LoFaso (Guitar/Vocals) performed a stripped-down set for us."
        "Tart Vandelay  builds on the sounds of indie rock, incorporating powerful vocal loops, as"
        "well as jazz-and-blues influenced guitar riffs. The musicianship of these two performers"
        "cannot be praised highly enough. I had to take a step back after hearing Katie reach a handful"
        "of breathtakingly high notes with such strength, and witnessing Martin effortlessly shred"
        "on the guitar. The band encompasses a modern indie/electronic sound, almost like a bluesier"
        "Dirty Projectors, with an emphasis on powerful vocals and mindboggling harmonies.\n\n"

        "These were merely two of the acts who caught my eye at the ArtAwake festival. Keep an eye"
        "out next Spring for this annual art and music festival, as this is one of the most diverse,"
        "local melting pot of musicians that you will stumble upon in Rochester!\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="bugjar_short_text">
        "Crawlin’ in the Bug Jar!\n\n"

        "By Nathan Raymond\n\n"

        "On a brisk night in late March, after driving through detours which were unaccounted for"
        "on my GPS, I parked my car along the side of the road in a neighborhood off of Monroe Avenue."
        "I was now within walking distance of my destination - Rochester’s beloved bar and concert venue,"
        "The Bug Jar. I had attended this venue several times to catch rock and punk shows, but tonight"
        "I would be experiencing three young local acts who would offer a variety of sounds including"
        "funk, soul, pop, and in some cases, ‘juice’. Hip Conspiracy, The Saplings, and Juicy Connotation"
        "would be taking the stage.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="bugjar_long_text">
        "Hip Conspiracy was the first of the three bands to perform. Their act consists entirely"
        "of University of Rochester students, and their sound is groovy, soulful, and captivating"
        "to say the least. The band immediately drew the audience’s attention by opening their set"
        "with a rendition of ‘Same Drugs’ by Chance the Rapper. Although Hip Conspiracy is a largely"
        "instrumental band, drummer Mike Abbot lent his voice to the tune, while the band supported"
        "him with a strong arrangement. Guitarist Luke Okerlund’s use of the lap steel guitar added"
        "twangy, sliding melodies which fit beautifully with their rendition of the piece. Another"
        "highlight of the band’s set was a track titled “When It Comes”, arranged by the band’s"
        "keyboardist Thomas Mariano. The song began with layers of atmospheric chords, slowly opening"
        "up to a point where Abbot switches the pulse from the hi-hat to the ride, and the keyboard"
        "takes on the melody. Luke Okerlund and Saxophonist, Sam Schachter (performing in place of"
        "Sean Levin and Miles Meth), each had their turn to rip solos as the song powered along,"
        "while Josh Miller maintained a chill walking bass lick. The group eventually resolved into a"
        "calm, concise outro.\n\n"

        "Next, it was The Saplings’ turn to party. This group is composed of nine musicians, primarily"
        "students who attend the Eastman School of Music. Their sound is exciting, and very difficult"
        "to define in just a few words. The Saplings’ art contains the catchiness of pop and the energy"
        "and technicality of prog-rock with an exuberant horn section, yet at times mellowing out to"
        "capture a Buddy Holly-esque early rock-and-roll vibe. The nine of them crammed together on"
        "The Bug Jar stage, but the tight space didn’t stop them from maintaining an infectiously"
        "energetic stage presence. The band performed several tracks from their debut EP, with pianist"
        "Abe Nouri and guitarist Greg Roberts splitting lead vocal and writing responsibilities."
        "Matt Bent (drums) and Ryder Eaton (bass) often lent their vocal talents to create impressively"
        "powerful four-part harmonies. One standout of the performance was the track, ‘Gonna Be a While’."
        "The unforgettable vocal melodies, pleasing harmonies, and the punchy chime of Nouri’s Rhodes"
        "piano all combined to create a crafty retro-pop tune that kept the entire room smiling.\n\n"
    </string>


    <string name="short_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"</string>

    <string name="large_text">
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="dr_griffs_title_text">Dr. Griffs</string>
    <string name="text_the_little_box">The Little Box</string>

    <string name="title_juicy_connotation">Juicy Connotation</string>
    <string name="del_paxton">Album Review: Del Paxton</string>
    <string name="title_rosehip">Album Review: Rosehip</string>
    <string name="title_wagoneer">Album Review: Grand Wagoneer</string>
    <string name="title_artawake">Gig: Art Awake 2017</string>
    <string name="title_bugjar">Gig: Bugjar</string>

    <string name="title_activity_fullscreen">FullscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="text_scan_qr_code">Scan</string>
    <string name="text_no_saves">No saved media yet!</string>



</resources>