<resources>
    <string name="player_error">Error initializing YouTube player: %s</string>
    <string name="seek_to">Jump To</string>
    <string name="seek_to_hint">Seconds</string>
    <string name="app_name">SounD CHK</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_camera">QR Code Reader</string>
    <string name="menu_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="menu_favorites">Favorites</string>
    <string name="text_read_QR">Reading QR Code...</string>
    <string name="title_activity_story_page">StoryPageActivity</string>

    <string name="read_more">".\nUnlock with QR Code to READ MORE\n."</string>

    <string name="paxton_short_text">
        "Del Paxton - “All Day, Every Day, All Night”\n\n"

        "By Nathan Raymond\n\n"

	    "Del Paxton is a three-piece rock group from Buffalo, New York which formed in 2013. With"
        "the help of Topshelf Records, the band released their debut full-length ‘All Day, Every Day"
        ", All Night’ on March 3rd, 2017. The release offers 11 songs, each infectiously catchy punk"
        "and pop-rock tunes with technical, math-rock undertones.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="paxton_long_text">
        "While Del Paxton’s music is often energetic, loud, and crunchy, there are plenty of"
        "atmospheric guitar riffs and vocal harmonies to compliment this, resulting in an album that"
        "is both sonically and emotionally dynamic. Tracks such as ‘Loose Leaf’ and ‘Wrong Distance’"
        "affirm the band’s driving punk and emo influences, while ‘Koolwink’ and ‘Thermos’ channel"
        "more of a pop-rock delivery.\n\n"

        "Guitarist and vocalist, Dylan England, writes lyrics that are both memorable and highly"
        "relatable, often regarding day-to-day activities such as taking long drives or embarking"
        "on introspective walks home. Bassist, Zack Schoedel, offers harmonies to add depth to"
        "Dylan’s catchy vocal melodies, and he even takes the lead with his own smart, personal"
        "lyrics on tracks such as ‘Take It To The Limit’ and ‘Primetime’. While Dylan executes"
        "well-crafted leads, and Zack rips technically-configured melodies, all of this is held"
        "together by Greg McClure’s tasteful drumming. Greg cleverly incorporates jerky shifts in"
        "rhythm and spastic fills to guide Dylan and Zack towards unexpected changes in tempo."
        "This makes listening to Del Paxton a highly interesting and involved experience. Whether"
        "you’re a fan of angsty emo-revival bands such as Snowing, or if you have a soft spot for"
        "90’s pop-rock groups like Third Eye Blind, there is no shortage of beautifully-constructed,"
        "heartfelt tracks for you to enjoy.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="rosehip_short_text">
        "Rosehip - “Sore”\n\n"

        "By Nick Raymond\n\n"

        "If you’re looking for an atmospheric, acoustic singer-songwriter record that’s extremely relaxing but equally emotional, then look no further than"
        "Rosehip’s new EP titled Sore. These five tracks consist of lush acoustic guitars which perfectly complement the gentle voice of Mackenzie Harris.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="rosehip_long_text">
        "While Sore is a sonically pleasant listen, Rosehip’s melancholy, detailed lyrics are what"
        "give these tracks depth. Whether she is contemplating her relationship with her parents,"
        "such as in the opening track, “6:28 AM”, or ruminating on a lost love on “Unruly Lover”,"
        "Rosehip has the power to transport the listener into her emotional state by using only a"
        "few words.\n\n"

        "While the bulk of this EP is filled with angst and sadness, there are some playful and"
        "humorous lyrics on the standout track “14th Colony”. As the record’s sole upbeat tune,"
        "this pop-influenced track provides a refreshing change of pace by showcasing charisma and"
        "personality. The second verse is particularly care-free, as Rosehip sings  “Let's get"
        "married today / Blind eye to what is happening / Even if we're not in love, / The tax"
        "breaks cut it I'm sure” over a staccatoed acoustic rhythm. But before it ends, Rosehip"
        "flips the song on it’s head by giving a gloomier depiction of not being in love"
        "(“But it's true, what they say We're not in love, none to blame 'Cause I'm inclined to"
        "stop short from the start). This clever trick allows “14th Colony” to flow seamlessly"
        "into the rest of the otherwise downcast EP. All in all, this record is the perfect"
        "soundtrack to a grey-skied, rainy afternoon. If a full length record from Rosehip is in"
        "the cards, it will undoubtedly be worth a listen.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="wagoneer_short_text">
        "Grand Wagoneer - “Reservoir”\n\n"

        "By Nick Raymond\n\n"

        "“I\'d self describe as a non-believing acolyte\nhalf-heartedly agreeing to everything to avoid a fight“"

        "\n\nThese are the first words sung on Grand Wagoneer\’s debut record titled Reservoir. The"
        "confessional and intimate lyrics here are a good indication of the story that will be told"
        "throughout the album. Nostalgia for love lost, self-deprecation, and religion are some of"
        "the recurring themes that Grand Wagoneer - aka Ben Schmitz - analyzes with sharp detail"
        "and stunning imagery on many of the tracks. Lyrically, this album fits snuggly into the "
        "recent wave of sadcore/emo music that has been sweeping the underground as of late.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="wagoneer_long_text">
        "But while the direct, emotional lyrics are the core of the record, it is the varied instrumentation that makes this body"
        "of work stand out from the rest. The opening track, “Diplomat”, takes the form of a mellow singer/songwriter tune with shimmering,"
        "layered acoustic guitars, tinged by plucking banjos and a mesmerizing keyboard riff that drives the song. What makes Reservoir so"
        "special is its authentic blend of many different genres, all of which Schmitz pulls off earnestly and effortlessly.\n\n"

        "The album’s third track is the true gem of the album. “Charlotte” is a piano-driven, Ben Folds-esque tune accompanied by"
        "epic baroque style horns. The narrative is a sad tale about a first love forbidden by his parents due to their religious beliefs."
        "But the grand instrumentation emphasizes the joy of the relationship, rather than ruminating on its abrupt demise.\n\n"

        "Many of the following songs make use of the electric guitar - particularly on the brooding track appropriately titled"
        "“Thumping and Thrashing”, and the energetic interlude “The Year in Review”, which sounds inspired by 90s indie bands"
        "such as Built to Spill.\n\n"

        "For an album of 11 songs, this record covers a lot of musical ground. Alternating between soft acoustic music such as"
        "on the minimalistic ballad “Say Goodbye”, guitar-driven indie rock on “Empire State”, and electronic loops on the"
        "reflective title track, is not an easy task. But Schmitz doesn’t just makes it work - he makes it work incredibly well."
        "As a result, Reservoir is a musically unpredictable, lyrically relatable, and wholly impressive record that is an extremely"
        "satisfying listening experience.\n\n"
    </string>


    <string name="artawake_short_text">
        "ArtAwake 2017!\n\n"

        "By Nathan Raymond\n\n"

        "Each year, students at the University of Rochester who are determined to promote the"
        "presence of art and music in our community join forces to host ArtAwake – an all-day art"
        "and music festival featuring a beautiful variety of art installations and music performances"
        "by local artists. On April 8th, the event was held at Rettner Hall on the University of"
        "Rochester campus. I managed to catch a few of the musical acts, and I was wildly impressed with what I heard.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="artawake_long_text">
        "Performing right outside of Rettner hall in the calm Spring air, I caught ‘Simba Marimba’,"
        "an African music group from the Eastman School of Music. The ensemble consists of only"
        "percussive instruments, all various types of marimbas aside from the drum set. The marimbas"
        "dramatically range in size, where the smaller high-pitched instruments hold the melody,"
        "and the larger lower-pitched marimbas are used for rhythm and bass. The tunes that the"
        "ensemble played were all joyful, enthusiastic, and incredibly technical. Playing these advanced"
        "marimba parts must have demanded some serious hand-eye coordination skills. However, what"
        "was even more impressive was the degree to which the Simba Marimba ensemble’s music radiated"
        "love and happiness in their art. This was clearly evident by a quick survey of the audience,"
        "as we all watched with wonder and smiles upon our faces.\n\n"

        "Another highlight of the evening was catching Tart Vandelay perform on the third floor of"
        "Rettner Hall. While the full-band typically contains four members, Katie Halligan"
        "(Vocals/Synth/Ukelele) and Martin LoFaso (Guitar/Vocals) performed a stripped-down set for us."
        "Tart Vandelay  builds on the sounds of indie rock, incorporating powerful vocal loops, as"
        "well as jazz-and-blues influenced guitar riffs. The musicianship of these two performers"
        "cannot be praised highly enough. I had to take a step back after hearing Katie reach a handful"
        "of breathtakingly high notes with such strength, and witnessing Martin effortlessly shred"
        "on the guitar. The band encompasses a modern indie/electronic sound, almost like a bluesier"
        "Dirty Projectors, with an emphasis on powerful vocals and mindboggling harmonies.\n\n"

        "These were merely two of the acts who caught my eye at the ArtAwake festival. Keep an eye"
        "out next Spring for this annual art and music festival, as this is one of the most diverse,"
        "local melting pot of musicians that you will stumble upon in Rochester!\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="bugjar_short_text">
        "Crawlin’ in the Bug Jar!\n\n"

        "By Nathan Raymond\n\n"

        "On a brisk night in late March, after driving through detours which were unaccounted for"
        "on my GPS, I parked my car along the side of the road in a neighborhood off of Monroe Avenue."
        "I was now within walking distance of my destination - Rochester’s beloved bar and concert venue,"
        "The Bug Jar. I had attended this venue several times to catch rock and punk shows, but tonight"
        "I would be experiencing three young local acts who would offer a variety of sounds including"
        "funk, soul, pop, and in some cases, ‘juice’. Hip Conspiracy, The Saplings, and Juicy Connotation"
        "would be taking the stage.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="bugjar_long_text">
        "Hip Conspiracy was the first of the three bands to perform. Their act consists entirely"
        "of University of Rochester students, and their sound is groovy, soulful, and captivating"
        "to say the least. The band immediately drew the audience’s attention by opening their set"
        "with a rendition of ‘Same Drugs’ by Chance the Rapper. Although Hip Conspiracy is a largely"
        "instrumental band, drummer Mike Abbot lent his voice to the tune, while the band supported"
        "him with a strong arrangement. Guitarist Luke Okerlund’s use of the lap steel guitar added"
        "twangy, sliding melodies which fit beautifully with their rendition of the piece. Another"
        "highlight of the band’s set was a track titled “When It Comes”, arranged by the band’s"
        "keyboardist Thomas Mariano. The song began with layers of atmospheric chords, slowly opening"
        "up to a point where Abbot switches the pulse from the hi-hat to the ride, and the keyboard"
        "takes on the melody. Luke Okerlund and Saxophonist, Sam Schachter (performing in place of"
        "Sean Levin and Miles Meth), each had their turn to rip solos as the song powered along,"
        "while Josh Miller maintained a chill walking bass lick. The group eventually resolved into a"
        "calm, concise outro.\n\n"

        "Next, it was The Saplings’ turn to party. This group is composed of nine musicians, primarily"
        "students who attend the Eastman School of Music. Their sound is exciting, and very difficult"
        "to define in just a few words. The Saplings’ art contains the catchiness of pop and the energy"
        "and technicality of prog-rock with an exuberant horn section, yet at times mellowing out to"
        "capture a Buddy Holly-esque early rock-and-roll vibe. The nine of them crammed together on"
        "The Bug Jar stage, but the tight space didn’t stop them from maintaining an infectiously"
        "energetic stage presence. The band performed several tracks from their debut EP, with pianist"
        "Abe Nouri and guitarist Greg Roberts splitting lead vocal and writing responsibilities."
        "Matt Bent (drums) and Ryder Eaton (bass) often lent their vocal talents to create impressively"
        "powerful four-part harmonies. One standout of the performance was the track, ‘Gonna Be a While’."
        "The unforgettable vocal melodies, pleasing harmonies, and the punchy chime of Nouri’s Rhodes"
        "piano all combined to create a crafty retro-pop tune that kept the entire room smiling.\n\n"
    </string>


    <string name="short_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"</string>

    <string name="large_text">
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="dr_griffs_title_text">Dr. Griffs</string>
    <string name="text_the_little_box">The Little Box</string>

    <string name="title_juicy_connotation">Juicy Connotation</string>
    <string name="del_paxton">Album Review: Del Paxton</string>
    <string name="title_rosehip">Album Review: Rosehip</string>
    <string name="title_wagoneer">Album Review: Grand Wagoneer</string>
    <string name="title_artawake">Gig: Art Awake 2017</string>
    <string name="title_bugjar">Gig: Bugjar</string>

    <string name="title_activity_fullscreen">FullscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="text_scan_qr_code">Scan</string>
    <string name="text_no_saves">No saved media yet!</string>



</resources>